<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>lstep.xyz</title>
  <subtitle>A blog by Loren.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://lstep.xyz/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://lstep.xyz/" />
  <updated>2025-03-25T10:47:40Z</updated>
  <id>https://lstep.xyz/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Loren</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>So You&#39;re Thinking About Monetizing Your Blog</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/so-youre-thinking-about-monetizing-your-blog/" />
    <updated>2024-07-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/so-youre-thinking-about-monetizing-your-blog/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on July 13, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steve at An Almost Anonymous Blog &lt;a href=&quot;https://lwgrs.bearblog.dev/paywalls-pain-and-balance/&quot;&gt;writing about paywalls:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wrote to myself yesterday saying that I&#39;m resigned to the fact that I&#39;m not going to make &amp;quot;serious&amp;quot; money online. On one hand, it sucks to think that I have all these big plans for myself and realize that no, I&#39;m not going to make a living out of this. On the other hand, it&#39;s freeing: I can write anything I want without worrying about the quality, or feel like I need to be a &amp;quot;content creator&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lately, I&#39;ve noticed a growing trend among fellow indie bloggers attempting to monetize their blog. It&#39;s become apparent that something fundamental has changed. The content I once enjoyed reading regularly has changed, and unfortunately, not for the better. These bloggers seem to be adjusting their writing style and content strategy, likely in pursuit of attracting more subscribers. And the frequency of their posts has increased, but the substance has dwindled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question that lingers is whether the income generated from these efforts significantly impacts their lives financially. I bet that in 99.9% of cases it doesn&#39;t. By switching to a monetized model for your blog you will probably piss off a lot of your faithful readers. So why bother?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Social Media</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/social-media/" />
    <updated>2024-07-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/social-media/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on July 24, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey friends, let&#39;s talk social media. It&#39;s been around forever, and you know what? I gotta confess, I&#39;ve never been a huge fan. Facebook, Instagram, TikTok, Snapchat – I’ve had an account on any of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The closest I came was Twitter. Used to have it on and off, mainly to keep up with current events. But after that whole thing with the shitposter buying XTwitter I said fuck this and deleted my account for good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a while now, I&#39;ve been on Mastodon. It&#39;s a different platform, but honestly? Here&#39;s the thing: everyone I follow there also has a blog with an RSS feed that follow. And guess what? The stuff I see on Mastodon is the same stuff I’ve already seen in those feeds. There&#39;s some occasional back-and-forth but for conversations I much prefer email. You can always reach me through my blog if you ever want to chat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, after a lot of thinking, I&#39;ve decided to ditch Mastodon too. Social media, just ain&#39;t my thing. I&#39;ll still be here on the blog, creating and sharing my thoughts. Just minus the social media.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Advice on Blogging</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/advice-on-blogging/" />
    <updated>2024-07-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/advice-on-blogging/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on July 27, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.jim-nielsen.com/2023/advice-on-blogging/&quot;&gt;Jim Nielsen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What my blog is now is a result of me wrestling with what it even means to blog. What I love about “blogging” is how personal it is. Even the word, “blog”, doesn’t give you any classifying genre of what content or experience you’ll get from any one individual’s blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blogging is all about personal expression. The best part? You never know what you&#39;ll get from someone&#39;s blog, making each one a unique discovery.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>RSS Versus Bookmarks</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/rss-versus-bookmarks/" />
    <updated>2024-08-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/rss-versus-bookmarks/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on August 03, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coincidentally I read two blog posts about RSS within days of each other this week. Chris is emphasizing the benefits of RSS and encouraging folks to start using it while Jason has decided to stop using it. So I thought I would chime in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://thoughts.uncountable.uk/request-for-iphone-rss-help/&quot;&gt;Chris&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Request for iPhone RSS help&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I actually prefer if &lt;a href=&quot;https://thoughts.uncountable.uk/id-rather-you-didnt-read-this/&quot;&gt;you read my blog over RSS&lt;/a&gt; than the web, for two reasons. Firstly, you have more chance of seeing my future posts that way, rather than remembering to visit the website again. But secondly, and more importantly, I think you will have an improved digital life if you incorporate RSS into your daily habits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jasonjournals.com/posts/no-need-for-feeds&quot;&gt;Jason&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Need For Feeds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to try something old-school, relatively “low-tech” and “slow-tech.” I deleted my RSS Reader app (NetNewsWire) from all my devices. And I have no web bookmarks to Feedly. But how would I keep up with the latest? What about the cool sites I follow? Answer: &lt;em&gt;surf the web!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I simply rely on my browser’s &lt;strong&gt;bookmarks&lt;/strong&gt;. I made a folder called, “RSS Replacement” and saved all the sites that I like to visit for new articles. So I more &lt;em&gt;intentionally&lt;/em&gt; go to my bookmark folder and click those I want to visit when I think to do so. I no longer feel pulled to frequently check an app — pull to refresh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I appreciate Jason&#39;s reasoning for deciding to stop using RSS but I side with Chris on this. I have been using RSS for as long as I can remember. Here&#39;s why: using RSS centralizes my favorite blogs and news sites, all in one place. I get real-time updates and I never miss a post from my favorite bloggers. Without RSS there is little chance that I would have ever seen the blog post above written by Chris and Jason.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Blogging Challenges - Are They Really Worth It?</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/blogging-challenges-are-they-really-worth-it/" />
    <updated>2024-08-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/blogging-challenges-are-they-really-worth-it/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on August 13, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an indie blogger, our unique voice is our biggest asset. Blogging challenges, especially those requiring daily posts, often lead to low-quality content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I prefer reading spontaneous posts that are authentic, not those written solely to meet a daily challenge goal. As a reader, I can easily tell the difference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Write when you have something genuine to share, rather than forcing content to meet a challenge deadline. Just my opinion!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Blogging - Eliminating Distractions</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/blogging-eliminating-distractions/" />
    <updated>2024-08-17T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/blogging-eliminating-distractions/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on August 17, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is Lionel &amp;quot;Ploum&amp;quot; Dricot &lt;a href=&quot;https://manuelmoreale.com/pb-ploum&quot;&gt;writing&lt;/a&gt; about his blog on &lt;a href=&quot;https://peopleandblogs.com/&quot;&gt;People and Blogs&lt;/a&gt;with Manu Moreale:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My blog is exactly where I want it to be. If I had to start again, I would simply do it like I did in 2022. I was quick to remove any form of comments from my blog and, later, any kind of statistics. As far as I know, I’m one of the few strong advocates for the complete removal of statistics/analytic/tracking tools. It’s not ethical to spy on users but it is also completely counterproductive. Statistics on websites are a brainworm. People are obsessed by it and it makes them write dumb stuff in order to increase a dumb counter. Getting rid of any audience-measuring tool is one of the best things I did in 2013.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve completely deleted all my social network accounts and never felt so free. Ironically, the less I was using social networks, the more readers I had on my blog. Social networks don’t bring you an audience. This is a lie! Social networks distract you from your real work and prevent your audience from reaching you. That’s their whole business! I know how frightening it is to delete permanently an account with thousands of followers. But this number is also a lie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This quote has prompted me to rethink my approach to this blog. While I’ve always valued the freedom to write what I want, the reminder to eliminate distractions like analytics and social media has hit home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve turned off analytics to focus more on the writing. I&#39;ve also eliminated social media letting my blog stand on its own merits. This feels like a step toward a better connection with my work and readers.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>15 blogging rules</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/15-blogging-rules/" />
    <updated>2024-09-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/15-blogging-rules/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on September 3, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give up on trying to be popular. I try not to filter myself based on what I believe will be popular. Some of my favourite posts get ignored. Some posts get popular and I have no idea why. Besides, terrible posts get buried fast if I’m posting three times a week. So post with abandon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give up on trying to be interesting. Readers will come to my site for what’s interesting to me, or not, it’s fine, just say what I think about whatever I’m thinking about.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://interconnected.org/home/2020/09/10/streak&quot;&gt;Matt Webb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Who am I responsible to here?</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/who-am-i-responsible-to-here/" />
    <updated>2024-09-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/who-am-i-responsible-to-here/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on September 3, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Whenever I change blogging platforms or domain names or simply post to several places, I feel a twinge of guilt. How will my “audience” feel about the changes? Does it confuse things?[…] I don’t get a lot of traffic, but it’s also not zero traffic, so I feel some responsibility. But why? I am not writing for money or influence or popularity. I write to better understand what I’m thinking about, and sometimes share the result. I write so that I have a record of those things. I write, almost entirely, for me.[…] In that light, I shouldn’t need to worry about whether my RSS feed is consistent or if people need to follow me in too many places. I don’t want to be a dick about it, but c’mon, it’s an unimportant personal blog by some nobody on the internet. Let’s not overthink it.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://baty.net/2024/07/who-am-i-responsible-to-here/&quot;&gt;Jack Baty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Write Like You Talk</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/write-like-you-talk/" />
    <updated>2024-09-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/write-like-you-talk/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on September 3, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Here&#39;s a simple trick for getting more people to read what you write: write in spoken language.[…] It seems to be hard for most people to write in spoken language. So perhaps the best solution is to write your first draft the way you usually would, then afterward look at each sentence and ask &amp;quot;Is this the way I&#39;d say this if I were talking to a friend?&amp;quot; If it isn&#39;t, imagine what you would say, and use that instead. After a while this filter will start to operate as you write. When you write something you wouldn&#39;t say, you&#39;ll hear the clank as it hits the page.[…] just don&#39;t let a sentence through unless it&#39;s the way you&#39;d say it to a friend.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paulgraham.com/talk.html&quot;&gt;Paul Graham&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>my morning walks with my dog Trixie</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/my-morning-walks-with-my-dog-trixie/" />
    <updated>2024-09-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/my-morning-walks-with-my-dog-trixie/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on September 23, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite things is my morning walks with my dog Trixie and listening to a podcast. We walk every morning rain, snow, wind, or freezing temperatures. We live in such a wonderful place. Our walks are usually about two miles. We walk out our long driveway to the road. The first thing we see is the farm across the street. Then, we turn left and walk to the neighborhood where everyone knows us, down to the main road, and then back up the long road to home, where everyone waves as they drive by. This has been a morning routine for going on 7 years.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Re - On personal websites and social web</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/re-on-personal-websites-and-social-web/" />
    <updated>2024-09-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/re-on-personal-websites-and-social-web/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on September 23, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, &lt;a href=&quot;https://manuelmoreale.com/on-personal-websites-and-social-web&quot;&gt;Manu reflects&lt;/a&gt; on the divide between two groups regarding the future of being social on the web.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And in those posts, I’m starting to see a trend of some sort. People are apparently starting to split into two camps that follow two very different ideological approaches when it comes to being social on the web. And when I say “people” I mean tech people, those who care about this type of stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other you have the people who are realising that maybe the solution is not to recreate social media but rather to abandon it and go back to a more deliberate way to be social online, using personal sites, small forums, emails, and other “traditional” tools. I’m obviously part of this second group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having said that I’m hopeful. I do think people are slowly starting to realise that you can get immense human value from the web outside of traditional social media. You have to work for it but it’s absolutely worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I side with Manu on this. Social Media is shit (my opinion). I’ve mentioned many times in the past that I’ve never had an account with any social media platforms that most people participate in, except for Twitter and Mastodon, both of which I’ve stopped using.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead, I’ve discovered indie blogging and indie blogs. I have over 100 in my RSS feed, and I add a few new ones every week. I find that indie blogging provides a better, more authentic experience than social media by offering thoughtful content without the distractions of ads and algorithms. Instead of chasing likes or viral trends, indie bloggers write with passion, giving readers deeper insights and unique perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, blogs create a more meaningful community where discussions feel genuine and less fleeting compared to social media’s fast-paced, superficial interactions. Bloggers also have full control over their content, free from the ever-changing algorithms that often limit visibility on social platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Re - Life&#39;s Simple Pleasures</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/re-lifes-simple-pleasures/" />
    <updated>2024-09-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/re-lifes-simple-pleasures/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on September 24, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lou Plummer, &lt;a href=&quot;https://louplummer.lol/life-s-simple-pleasures/&quot;&gt;writing about one of life’s simple pleasures&lt;/a&gt;, said, “Give me a styrofoam tray of authentic tacos from a trailer in a convenience store parking lot selling authentic Mexican street food, and I will be happy.” This made me realize how much I miss good Mexican food. My favorite meal: two cheese enchiladas with rice and beans. When I lived in Southern California, I knew all the best spots for excellent Mexican food. Seven years ago, we moved to New Jersey, and I’m still searching for a place that serves real, authentic Mexican food.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Re - How I find interesting blogs</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/re-how-i-find-interesting-blogs/" />
    <updated>2024-09-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/re-how-i-find-interesting-blogs/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on September 30, 2024 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like this conversation so I thought I would chime in: it revolves around how different bloggers discover new blogs. &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.bjhess.com/2024/09/13/i-appreciate-personal.html&quot;&gt;Barry Hess&lt;/a&gt; mentions submitting his blog to various directories but notes limited traffic from them. &lt;a href=&quot;https://jrn.sh/post/how-i-find-interesting-blogs&quot;&gt;JRN&lt;/a&gt;responds, saying they prefer discovering blogs through bloggers linking to or responding to each other, social platforms like Mastodon, and blog exploration features on platforms like Micro.blog. And &lt;a href=&quot;https://thoughts.uncountable.uk/re-how-i-find-interesting-blogs/&quot;&gt;Chris&lt;/a&gt; at “uncountable thoughts” echoes JRN’s sentiment, emphasizing that blog directories aren’t heavily used for discovery; instead, contextual cross-linking between blogs is a more effective method.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m relatively new to the indie blogging, so I’m always on the lookout for new blogs to follow. What works best for me is when I come across a blog that references another one I almost always click through, check out the “About” page, and skim the article archives to see if their content interests me. If it does, I’ll add their blog to my RSS feed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For instance, if you’ve stumbled upon this blog post, you have the chance to discover three new blogs, in addition to mine!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bjhess.com/&quot;&gt;Barry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jrn.sh/&quot;&gt;JRN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://thoughts.uncountable.uk/&quot;&gt;Chris&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Update on lstep.xyz</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/update-on-lstepxyz/" />
    <updated>2025-02-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/update-on-lstepxyz/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 1, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2024, I picked up the lstep.xyz domain with the idea of using it as a space to blog about non-tech stuff. All my tech related writing happens over at &lt;a href=&quot;https://ldstephens.me/&quot;&gt;ldstephens.me&lt;/a&gt;. But honestly? The way I’ve used it so far has been all over the place. I hosted it on Pika off and on, but I was never fully settled on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lately, I’ve been thinking about moving it to a static site. I finally did it. The biggest reason was that I didn’t want to be tied to a platform. That’s exactly why I moved ldstephens.me to a static site too. Sure, I love the technical challenge, but more than that, I wanted full control. Platforms change, they shut down, and they enforce rules. When you own your own site, you make the rules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog is mine. I built it myself, and I’m proud of that. Now I can do whatever the hell I want with it. It’s my own little corner of the internet. When you run your own site, you control everything. The content, the design, the URLs everything. No middlemen, no restrictions. Just a direct line between me and whoever stops by to read.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and if you’ve been following via RSS, don’t worry. I’ve set up a 301 redirect, so your feed should keep working just fine.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>On Don&#39;t Make a Blog, Make a Brain Dump</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/link-post-dont-make-a-blog-make-a-brain-dump/" />
    <updated>2025-02-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/link-post-dont-make-a-blog-make-a-brain-dump/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 2, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://btxx.org/posts/dump/#menu&quot;&gt;Bradley Taunt, btxx.org&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another problem arises when you finally do convince someone to start “blogging” online; self-doubt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“What could I possibly have to share?”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“What if everyone hates what I post?”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“What if my content sucks?”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just dump it. Who cares. It’s the internet after all, so who are you trying to impress? The point is that your sharing your own experiences that are unique to you as an individual. Posting something that you think is pointless or mundane might be extremely helpful or, at the very least, entertaining for someone else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Write up what you did over the weekend, a new recipe you tried out, review a movie/book or video game you enjoyed, list step-by-step instructions on how you installed a new appliance in your house - anything! Just write and be part of what made the internet fun, exciting and personal again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>“Unplatform” a guidebook for escaping social media</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/unplatform-a-guidebook-for-escaping-social-media/" />
    <updated>2025-02-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/unplatform-a-guidebook-for-escaping-social-media/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 2, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://unplatform.fromthesuperhighway.com/&quot;&gt;Unplatform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unplatform is an interactive guidebook, online library, and recommendations database intended to help you escape social media and join the indie web.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m not on social media, but I’m a big fan of having your own space on the indie web. If you’re thinking about quitting social media, this guidebook is definitely worth checking out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>11ty project update</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/11ty-project-update/" />
    <updated>2025-02-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/11ty-project-update/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 3, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My attempt at replicating this site using 11ty was a complete failure. The skills required for the project are beyond my capabilities. The site works great as is with pure &lt;a href=&quot;https://htmlforpeople.com/&quot;&gt;HTML and CSS&lt;/a&gt; which I know how to manage.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>11ty project</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/11ty-project/" />
    <updated>2025-02-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/11ty-project/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 3, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I decided to replicate this site in 11ty as a learning project. The first thing I did was install Node.js. When I came to the 11ty install step, the install failed. After some additional attempts, I determined the problem might be the version of Node.js that I installed. So I uninstalled Node.js. Today, I’ll install a different version and start over.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>How I use AI for writing and coding</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/how-i-use-ai-for-writing-and-coding/" />
    <updated>2025-02-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/how-i-use-ai-for-writing-and-coding/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 6, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been using AI in two ways: for help with my writing and for figuring out how to do things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My writing skills aren’t that great. I know what I want to say and how I want to say it, but I struggle to put it into words. So, I use AI to proofread and improve the structure of what I’ve written.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other way AI helps me is with writing HTML and CSS for my static blog projects. I use it to explain things in HTML or CSS and to offer the code. For example, yesterday, I had a couple of posts where I kept getting an error in my HTML, and I couldn’t figure out what was wrong. So, I copied the code and put it into Claude. It rewrote the code and explained what it fixed. I guess you could call that debugging my code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AI has become a valuable tool for me. Whether it’s helping me improve my writing or troubleshooting code, it saves me time and makes things easier.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Re - No, The People Didn’t Vote For This</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/re-no-the-people-didnt-vote-for-this/" />
    <updated>2025-02-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/re-no-the-people-didnt-vote-for-this/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 10, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Democrats, obviously, aren’t thrilled, but the more meaningful data is that &lt;a href=&quot;https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/5129353-gop-support-for-musk-influence-with-trump-falls-dramatically-poll/&quot;&gt;Republicans don’t like what Elon Musk is doing&lt;/a&gt; at all.[…] Voters who supported Trump based on economic promises are instead seeing federal support for their local hospitals vanish, government contracts that supported thousands of local jobs disappear, and consumer prices continue to rise. The very voters who wanted economic stability are getting the opposite: economic chaos driven by an unelected billionaire’s personal agenda.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techdirt.com/2025/02/10/no-the-people-didnt-vote-for-this/&quot;&gt;Mike Masnick&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well! Well! Well! Lied to!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Sorry for all the test posts today</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/sorry-for-all-the-test-posts-today/" />
    <updated>2025-02-16T21:24:26Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/sorry-for-all-the-test-posts-today/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 16, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey friends, sorry for all the test posts today. I’m working on getting the RSS feed working properly, and the only way to know if it’s working correctly is with test posts.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Test 2</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/test2/" />
    <updated>2025-02-17T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/test2/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 17, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Testing the RSS feed?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Live on 11ty at Last!</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/live-on-11ty-at-last/" />
    <updated>2025-02-17T16:11:34Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/live-on-11ty-at-last/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 17, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The site is finally live on 11ty! Still working on getting the RSS feed running properly--doing it manually for now. If you&#39;re an 11ty pro and can help, shoot me an email.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Let&#39;s see how this goes</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/lets-see-how-this-goes/" />
    <updated>2025-02-18T13:10:51Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/lets-see-how-this-goes/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 18, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I installed the 11ty RSS plugin. This is my first since installing it so if you get this post in your RSS feed then it’s working.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s a cold morning in New Jersey 20° with a wind chill of 18°. Not supposed to get out of the 20’s all day. Looks like we’ll be confined indoors all day so I’ll work on building my other blog in 11ty.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>From Static HTML to Eleventy</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/from-static-html-to-eleventy/" />
    <updated>2025-02-19T19:54:52Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/from-static-html-to-eleventy/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 19, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the title suggests, this blog is now generated using &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.11ty.dev/&quot;&gt;Eleventy&lt;/a&gt; also known as 11ty. You might remember that I had planned to rebuild the blog using 11ty, and after a lot of trial and error, I finally made it happen. The process wasn&#39;t easy, but I&#39;ve learned a ton.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The difference between a plain static site and one generated with Eleventy is huge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When managing a static site manually, everything had to be created and organized by hand HTML, CSS, and all the files. Each page was its own separate HTML file, so if something like the navigation needed updating, every page had to be changed individually. There was no templating, no automation just raw HTML, written line by line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With Eleventy and Nunjucks, things are much easier. Content can be written in Markdown or Nunjucks templates, and Eleventy takes care of generating the final HTML. Instead of repeating the same structure on every page, layouts can be created and reused. Updates are simple--changing a single template regenerates the entire site. Data from JSON files or APIs can be pulled in to dynamically create pages. It&#39;s a much more efficient and flexible way to manage a static site compared to doing everything manually. And, the Eleventy RSS plugin automatically updates and processes an RSS feed whenever a new post is added.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Quoting Tracy Durnell</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/quoting-tracy-durnell/" />
    <updated>2025-02-20T17:23:08Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/quoting-tracy-durnell/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 20, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Employ private posts — I don’t have to publish everything I write&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://tracydurnell.com/2025/01/21/guiding-principles-for-my-website/&quot;&gt;Tracy Durnell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Kindle Paperwhite’s annoying flashes</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/kindle-paperwhites-annoying-flashes/" />
    <updated>2025-02-20T22:11:49Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/kindle-paperwhites-annoying-flashes/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 20, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nice-marmot.net/Archives/2025/February_2025.html#note_2766&quot;&gt;Dave Rogers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a 10th generation Kindle Paperwhite. I&#39;ve read from it a fair amount, particularly when I was away, because it&#39;s so light. But I generally don&#39;t care for the experience. It&#39;s very slow, and whenever I turn a page I get this annoying flash as the screen goes through this inversion process from whatever mode I&#39;m in until it settles on either the Dark or Light Mode, which I selected. That is, if I&#39;m in Light Mode, the page will first appear in Dark Mode, then switch to Light Mode. If I&#39;m in Dark Mode and turn the page, the page first appears in Light Mode, then switches to dark. Very annoying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also have a Paperwhite that I use for reading, and while I appreciate its lightweight, I’m not a huge fan of the overall experience either. I continue to use it because it’s so lightweight. I have an iPad, but it’s simply too heavy for comfortable reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now, I’m actually reading a physical book for the first time in a very long time, and I’m enjoying the experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Prickly peril</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/prickly-peril/" />
    <updated>2025-02-24T17:03:17Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/prickly-peril/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 24, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, a day warm enough to get outside. It was all about reclaiming a bit of our property from the wild. First on the agenda was trimming back those scraggly dead tree branches along the driveway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the challenge was the greenbrier. If you&#39;ve ever dealt with this, you know what I’m talking about. Common greenbrier is native to the eastern US, and it&#39;s made itself at home in our woodlands. They form dense, almost impenetrable thickets that take over everything. They have seriously sharp prickles. I learned that lesson despite wearing gloves. It&#39;s like botanical barbed wire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, I tackled a section of the thicket where our woodlands border the yard. It was a battle, to say the least. Cutting, pulling, and trying to avoid getting snagged by those vicious thorns. It&#39;s amazing how quickly this plant can take over.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Platforms own you, not vice versa</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/platforms-own-you-not-vice-versa/" />
    <updated>2025-02-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/platforms-own-you-not-vice-versa/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on February 26, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2025/02/25/chegg-google-ai-lawsuit/&quot;&gt;Hannah Ziegler&lt;/a&gt;, The Washington Post&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Online education company Chegg sues Google, says AI is killing business A new lawsuit against Google alleges that the search giant’s artificial intelligence summaries have hurt online education company Chegg’s traffic and revenue so much that the company may not survive in its current form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chegg, which provides students with homework help and test answers, filed the suit against Google and parent company Alphabet this week in federal court. In its quarterly report released Monday, the company tied its recent financial struggles to AI-generated search summaries and claimed Google has “unjustly retained traffic” that once flowed to Chegg’s site. Chegg reported $144 million in revenue in its fourth quarter, a 24 percent decrease from the same period last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chegg&#39;s pissed because Google isn&#39;t sending them traffic any more. Welcome to the club. If your business relies on another company&#39;s platform, you&#39;re a tenant with no lease. Chegg&#39;s lawsuit? Probably a long shot. The lesson? The landlord can do whatever the hell they want and a public company like Chegg should know better than to rely on someone else’s platform.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Why write when no one’s reading?</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/why-write-when-no-ones-reading/" />
    <updated>2025-03-02T15:06:59Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/why-write-when-no-ones-reading/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on March 2, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing without an audience might feel pointless. It isn’t just about being read; it’s about thinking more clearly. Putting thoughts into words forces us to process them in a way passive consumption doesn&#39;t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But most of all, write because your voice matters even if only to you. And if just one person finds what you write useful, then that makes it even more worthwhile. I think about the things I’ve read that have stuck with me, and I hope my words can do the same for someone else.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Quoting Zsolt Benke</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/quoting-zsolt-benke/" />
    <updated>2025-03-07T10:03:21Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/quoting-zsolt-benke/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on March 7, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;getting recognized as a blogger these days is rarely going to work. People are increasingly consuming different types of content these days, and this is largely due to the way AI is changing the way we interact with the web.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That said, having a blog for thinking out loud is still the best way to learn and then “report” it, even if we’re the only ones reading it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://decoding.io/2025/02/read-its-still-worth-blogging-in-the-age-of-ai/&quot;&gt;Zsolt Benke&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>PSA - Amazon will log all Echo voice commands starting March 28</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/psa-amazon-will-log-all-echo-voice-commands-starting-march-28/" />
    <updated>2025-03-15T16:38:14Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/psa-amazon-will-log-all-echo-voice-commands-starting-march-28/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on March 15, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t use Alexa but if you do you might want to consider if you want to continue using it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scharon Harding, &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2025/03/everything-you-say-to-your-echo-will-be-sent-to-amazon-starting-on-march-28/&quot;&gt;Ars Technica&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an email sent to customers today, Amazon said that Echo users will no longer be able to set their devices to process Alexa requests locally and, therefore, avoid sending voice recordings to Amazon’s cloud. Amazon apparently sent the email to users with “Do Not Send Voice Recordings” enabled on their Echo. Starting on March 28, recordings of everything spoken to the Alexa living in Echo speakers and smart displays will automatically be sent to Amazon and processed in the cloud.[…] there are plenty of reasons why people wouldn&#39;t want Amazon to receive recordings of what they say to their personal device. For one, the idea of a conglomerate being able to listen to personal requests made in your home is, simply, unnerving.[…] Amazon &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201602230&quot;&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; it allows employees to listen to Alexa voice recordings to train its speech recognition and natural language understanding systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Quoting - 16 March 2025 11:13 AM</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/quoting-16-march-2025-1113-am/" />
    <updated>2025-03-16T11:18:11Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/quoting-16-march-2025-1113-am/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on March 16, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;why write? like art i write not thinking about the reader but trying to compose my thoughts into some kind of cogent experience for me and bringing the reader along as sort of a secondary consideration. &lt;a href=&quot;https://mrbrianpuck.wordpress.com/2025/03/15/why-write-right/&quot;&gt;why write right&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It benefits literally everyone except Apple’s shareholders if people keep their devices for years longer. Durable technology is bad business. Apple, of course, built it’s name on quality, so they can’t make their products bad. They need to be good enough for the prices they command, but not so good that you keep them too long. &lt;a href=&quot;https://gomakethings.com/durable-technology/&quot;&gt;Durable technology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Quoting Barry Hess</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/quoting-barry-hess/" />
    <updated>2025-03-16T11:31:32Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/quoting-barry-hess/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on March 16, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blogging is a conversation. It’s a conversation with yourself and it’s a conversation with others.[…] You don’t have to be an essayist. (Though you can be one if you want!) Don’t let those essayists discourage you from blogging. Just write. Just blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bjhess.com/posts/you-re-a-blogger-not-an-essayist&quot;&gt;Barry Hess&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Apple ID phishing alert</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/apple-id-phishing-alert/" />
    <updated>2025-03-20T09:25:58Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/apple-id-phishing-alert/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on March 20, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey friends, just a heads-up for Mac users: there’s a &lt;a href=&quot;https://9to5mac.com/2025/03/20/this-is-one-of-the-most-sophisticated-phishing-attacks-ever-made-against-mac-users/&quot;&gt;new phishing scam&lt;/a&gt; going around. It starts with a fake security alert while you’re browsing, but this one goes a step further by freezing the page, making it seem like your Mac is locked making the scam feel more real. The goal is to trick you into entering your Apple ID and password.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you see one of these popups and the page is frozen, press Command + Option + Esc, select Safari, and force quit to force quit the app.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>This makes my fucking blood boil!</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/this-makes-my-fucking-blood-boil/" />
    <updated>2025-03-22T10:15:28Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/this-makes-my-fucking-blood-boil/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on March 22, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emily Peck,&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.axios.com/2025/03/21/social-security-lutnick-doge-checks&quot;&gt; writing for Axios&lt;/a&gt;: Seniors won&#39;t complain if they miss a Social Security check, Lutnick says&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Commerce secretary Howard Lutnick suggested this week that only &amp;quot;fraudsters&amp;quot; would complain about missing a monthly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.axios.com/2025/03/20/doge-social-security-deposit-fraud&quot;&gt;Social Security&lt;/a&gt; check, and that most people wouldn&#39;t mind if the government simply skipped a payment.[…] More than 70 million Americans get a Social Security benefit every month, and for many, those checks are their only income.[…] &amp;quot;Let&#39;s say Social Security didn&#39;t send out their checks this month. My mother-in-law, who&#39;s 94, she wouldn&#39;t call and complain,&amp;quot; Lutnick — a billionaire former Wall Street CEO — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=182ckTL2KBA&quot;&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; the billionaire &amp;quot;All In&amp;quot; podcast host Chamath Palihapitiya.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This kind of shit just makes my fucking blood boil. As many of you know you know I’m 80 years old. I depend on my monthly Social Security check to live. Would I miss a check? Hell yes! So would millions of other seniors Republicans, Democrats, Independents, and those who don’t give a shit about politics. For some, it’s their &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; source of income.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not like we’re getting a freebie here. We all paid into Social Security and Medicare our entire working lives. I started working when I was 15 years old and was never without a job until I retired. So I paid my fucking dues and so did all other seniors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, but sure, let&#39;s just skip a payment, what could possibly go wrong? Maybe Lutnick thinks we can all just hop on our yachts and ride out the month, or maybe we should start selling off our prescription meds to make rent. The sheer arrogance of a billionaire pretending he knows what it&#39;s like to rely on Social Security is bullshit. News flash: We&#39;re not asking for a favor. We&#39;re demanding what we &lt;em&gt;earned&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe you can tell I’m pissed. &lt;em&gt;Don’t fuck with our Social Security and Medicare!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Migrating an old blog from WordPress.com to Eleventy</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/migrating-an-old-blog-from-wordpresscom-to-eleventy/" />
    <updated>2025-03-23T10:08:57Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/migrating-an-old-blog-from-wordpresscom-to-eleventy/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on March 23, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve got this old blog over on &lt;a href=&quot;https://ldstephens.net&quot;&gt;WordPress.com&lt;/a&gt; that I don&#39;t post to anymore, but people still check it out. When it was time to renew the subscription, I just went with the free version. Now, every time you go there, there&#39;s a banner on the header of every page telling me to upgrade, and tons of fucking ads. It looks like shit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, the other day I found this article about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.11ty.dev/docs/migrate/wordpress/&quot;&gt;migrating blogs from WordPress to Eleventy&lt;/a&gt;. This blog is built with 11ty. So, I&#39;m trying to move the WordPress blog over to Eleventy. If it works out, I’ll deploy it on Netlify or Vercel.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Important Update - this blog has a new RSS Feed</title>
    <link href="https://lstep.xyz/posts/important-update-this-blog-has-a-new-rss-feed/" />
    <updated>2025-03-25T10:47:40Z</updated>
    <id>https://lstep.xyz/posts/important-update-this-blog-has-a-new-rss-feed/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Posted on March 25, 2025 by Loren&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone, just a quick heads-up--I&#39;m moving my blog from &lt;strong&gt;lstep.xyz&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://ldstephens.net&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ldstephens.net&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. If you follow via RSS, you&#39;ll need to update your feed settings to the new URL:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New RSS Feed:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://ldstephens.net/feed/feed.xml&quot;&gt;https://ldstephens.net/feed/feed.xml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for sticking around! See you at the new place. 🚀&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>